//starts quiz after DOCLoadingComplete
addEventListener("DOMContentLoaded", function () {
 let username = "";

function loadQuestion (){

};
//handles 
function handleTrueButtonClick(){

};
function handleFalseButtonClick(){

};

function showResults(){

};
//score variable
let score = 0;
//questions array of question:value, answer:value objects
let questions = [
    { question: "True or False:Irish film 'An Irish Goodbye'won the Oscar for Best Short Film. " , answer:true },
    { question: "True or False:The 2023 Rugby World Cup hosts are South Africa. ", answer: false},
    { question: "True or False: Michael D. Higgins and Leo Varadkar became the first ever President and Taoiseach to attend a British coronation.  ", answer: true },
    { question: "True or False: An Post moved is headquarters from the G.P.O to Cork.", answer: false },
    { question: "True or False: Ireland was represented in the Eurovision Song Contest 2023 by Hozier", answer: false },
    { question: "True or False: Limerck won the All Ireland senior hurling final for the fourth time in a row", answer: true },
    { question: "True or False: U.S. Vice President Kamala Harris made a state visit to Ireland in April", answer: false },
    { question: "True or False: Meta was fined â‚¬390 million by the Irish Data Protection Council", answer: true },
    { question: "True or False: Comedian Patrick Kielty took over as the new host of The Late Late Show", answer: true },
    { question: "True or False: The Irish Grand National was won by 'I Am Roy Keane', trained by Willie Mullins", answer: false },
];
//event listeners required
addEventListener("click", handleTrueButtonClick);
addEventListener("click", handleFalseButtonClick);
//username handle
document.getElementById("username");

);